很好，你完成了。我们从取消掉这段代码的注释开始
Alright, you're done. Let's start by uncommenting out that text.
你能看到，你需要这个forecast字符串
As you can see, you need that forecast string
传递给DetailActivity。
to pass on to our DetailActivity. So what do
所以我们要怎样获得这个forecast字符串呢？我们很幸运
we use to get that forecast string? Well we're lucky
因为我们实际上已经把这个AdapterView传递进来了
here, because we actually get the AdapterView passed in.
我们需要做的只是把它转化成SimpleCursorAdapter
All we have to do is cast it at simple
然后我们就能得到这个光标(cursor)
cursor adaptor and then we can get the cursor. We
我们把它移动到指定的地方。然后我们可以使用String.format
can move it to our position. Then, we can use string.format
基于列数来获得一个格式化的字符串
to get a formatted string based on the values
注意，这里的数列编号
of our columns. Note, once again the nice use
使用的很好。这是一个右花括号
of our column indexes. One ending curly brace and
把这些intent的东西移动到里面。这就完成了
let's move that intent stuff into there. And that's it.
现在我们要在屏幕上点击
Now we'll be able to click on it again
然后就会跳转到详细信息界面
and it'll actually go to our normal detail view.
我们来试一试。
Let's try it out. So here we are, there's
这是我们的列表界面，然后我们进到了详细信息。
our list view and we go right into details. Pretty
太酷了。但是如果我们把温度单位改成英制的
cool. However, if we change our temperature units to imperial here
这里却不会更新。要是它能够
doesn't actually update. It would be nice if that, it was
像这里一样使用相同的cursor模型，就更好了。
based on the same kind of cursor model we have here.
用某种方法监测设置
Something that was observing with the
然后相应的更新数据
content observer and would actually update.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
当我们改变设置时
When we changed our setting.